And-and I realize that she
stood up by remaining seated,
but now is not that time
to enjoy the irony of that.
(Sheldon:)Now, I ask you again.
(Sheldon:)Who here takes issue
with this person...?
(Woman:)Why should we listen to you?
You cut the line yourself.
(Sheldon:)I most certainly did not.
(Woman:)I saw you.
(Man:)If you're feeling dizzy,
(Man:)it's because the tables
have turned.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me, I paid someone
to wait in line for me,
(Sheldon:)and then
when I arrived,
(Sheldon:)he left, so what you
saw, my good woman,
was “swapsies”,
not “cutsies”.
Oh, no, no, no, no, wait!
(Sheldon:)I ask you all again.
A show of hands.
Who here takes issue...?
Well, stop moving!
He's gonna get in!
(Leonard:)Buddy, let it go.
No, I can't.
(Sheldon:)This isn't right.
(Leonard:)You did everything you could.
(Sheldon:)No, I could've done more.
(Leonard:)Now, now, you
denigrated the memory
(Leonard:)of a great civil
rights pioneer.
(Leonard:)That's all anyone could ask.
(Penny:)To be honest, I'm surprised you
cared about the wedding at all.
(Beverly:)I'm still human, Penny.
(Beverly:)Not getting invited
to my own son's wedding